import { QuizData } from "../types/quiz";

const questions: QuizData[] = [
  {
    city: "Seba Ayoun",
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "What is the name of the gate in Meknes that leads to the medina?",
        answers: ["Bab Mansour", "Bab Berdieyinne", "Bab Khmiss"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 0,
      },
      {
        question: "Which university is located in Meknes?",
        answers: [
          "Uni Mohammed V",
          "Uni Sidi Mohammed Ben Abdellah",
          "Uni Hassan II",
        ],
        correctAnswerIndex: 1,
      },
      {
        question:
          "What is the name of the historical area located on the outskirts of Meknes?",
        answers: ["Volubilis", "Chefchaouen", "Essaouira"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 0,
      },
      {
        question: "Which famous Moroccan poet is buried in Meknes?",
        answers: [
          "Ahmad ibn al-Qadi",
          "Mohammed Awzal",
          "Moulay Idris al-Azhar",
        ],
        correctAnswerIndex: 1,
      },
      {
        question: "What is the name of the palace located in Meknes?",
        answers: ["Bahia Palace", "El Badi Palace", "Dar el Makhzen"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 2,
      },
      {
        question:
          "What is the name of the mausoleum in Meknes that houses the tombs of Moulay Ismail and his family?",
        answers: [
          "Hassan Tower",
          "Mausoleum of Mohammed V",
          "Moulay Ismail Mausoleum",
        ],
        correctAnswerIndex: 2,
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    city: "Rabat",
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "What is the name of the gate in Rabat that leads to the medina?",
        answers: ["Bab Mansour", "Bab Berdieyinne", "Bab Khmiss"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 0,
      },
      {
        question: "Which university is located in Rabat?",
        answers: [
          "Université Mohammed V",
          "Université Sidi Mohammed Ben Abdellah",
          "Université Hassan II",
        ],
        correctAnswerIndex: 1,
      },
      {
        question:
          "What is the name of the historical area located on the outskirts of Meknes?",
        answers: ["Volubilis", "Chefchaouen", "Essaouira"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 0,
      },
      {
        question: "Which famous Moroccan poet is buried in Meknes?",
        answers: [
          "Ahmad ibn al-Qadi",
          "Mohammed Awzal",
          "Moulay Idris al-Azhar",
        ],
        correctAnswerIndex: 1,
      },
      {
        question: "What is the name of the palace located in Meknes?",
        answers: ["Bahia Palace", "El Badi Palace", "Dar el Makhzen"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 2,
      },
      {
        question:
          "What is the name of the mausoleum in Meknes that houses the tombs of Moulay Ismail and his family?",
        answers: [
          "Hassan Tower",
          "Mausoleum of Mohammed V",
          "Moulay Ismail Mausoleum",
        ],
        correctAnswerIndex: 2,
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    city: "Oujda",
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "What is the name of the gate in Oujda that leads to the medina?",
        answers: ["Bab Mansour", "Bab Berdieyinne", "Bab Khmiss"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 0,
      },
      {
        question: "Which university is located in Oujda?",
        answers: [
          "Université Mohammed V",
          "Université Sidi Mohammed Ben Abdellah",
          "Université Hassan II",
        ],
        correctAnswerIndex: 1,
      },
      {
        question:
          "What is the name of the historical area located on the outskirts of Meknes?",
        answers: ["Volubilis", "Chefchaouen", "Essaouira"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 0,
      },
      {
        question: "Which famous Moroccan poet is buried in Meknes?",
        answers: [
          "Ahmad ibn al-Qadi",
          "Mohammed Awzal",
          "Moulay Idris al-Azhar",
        ],
        correctAnswerIndex: 1,
      },
      {
        question: "What is the name of the palace located in Meknes?",
        answers: ["Bahia Palace", "El Badi Palace", "Dar el Makhzen"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 2,
      },
      {
        question:
          "What is the name of the mausoleum in Meknes that houses the tombs of Moulay Ismail and his family?",
        answers: [
          "Hassan Tower",
          "Mausoleum of Mohammed V",
          "Moulay Ismail Mausoleum",
        ],
        correctAnswerIndex: 2,
      },
    ],
  },
];

export default questions;
